<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>YANG on Visional</title>
    <link>https://visionallabs.com/tags/yang/</link>
    <description>Recent content in YANG on Visional</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 11:15:47 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://visionallabs.com/tags/yang/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Networks, Identify Yourselves!</title>
      <link>https://visionallabs.com/blog/networks-identify-yourselves/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 11:15:47 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://visionallabs.com/blog/networks-identify-yourselves/</guid>
      <description>YANG, a data modeling language, has revolutionized the field of networking by providing a standardized way to define and manage network configurations. Through its hierarchical structure, expressive syntax, and platform-agnostic nature, YANG enables interoperability, automation, and scalability in network management, paving the way for more efficient and agile network infrastructures.&#xA;What is YANG? In the ever-evolving landscape of networking, managing the complexity of modern networks efficiently has become paramount. Enter YANG (Yet Another Next Generation), a data modeling language standardized by the IETF (Internet Engineering Task Force), which has emerged as a game-changer in network configuration and management.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Of Yin And Yang</title>
      <link>https://visionallabs.com/blog/of-yin-and-yang/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 10:18:32 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://visionallabs.com/blog/of-yin-and-yang/</guid>
      <description>SNMP (Simple Network Management Protocol) and YANG (Yet Another Next Generation) are closely related technologies that play complementary roles in network management. SNMP serves as a protocol for monitoring and managing network devices, while YANG provides a data modeling language for defining the structure and semantics of network configurations. Together, SNMP and YANG form a powerful framework for orchestrating network operations, enabling administrators to monitor, configure, and optimize network infrastructure effectively.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
